cellmania.com 2013-03-19

# Cellmania - Leading Provider of M-commerce Solutions - Privacy Policy for Cellmania

The following privacy policy is specific to Cellmania.

Cellmania is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for www.cellmania.com. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our many offerings. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.

Some of our customers have requested that we minimize the amount of data entry and the number of times they have to enter their username and password. As part of solving this problem for our customers, we keep track of the IP address of the client machine and the username of the customer. We also keep an encrypted copy of the customer's password and use a timeout mechanism to ensure that someone else cannot login to the site as you, if you have left your machine unlocked for a long time. For greater security, we provide a "logout" button, which you can use to immediately logout of your session on our web site. You should use the logout option and exit out of the browser, if you are using our site from a "kiosk" location, where multiple people may be using the same machine for short periods of time.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Usually, this information is only used to notify the user for Cellmania's communications only. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

This site contains links to other sites. Cellmania is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our site uses a form for users to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address), unique identifiers. Contact information from the order form is used to send information to our customers. The customer's contact information is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Cellmania never shares your individual information with any third party except information used by our suppliers and carriers to fulfill the products and services you ordered. Cellmania uses 3rd party software and services to verify credit card information. Cellmania will only share aggregate user information with certain partners.

Contact information is used to notify customers when there is a response to their question from one of our experts or from a supplier or carrier. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We believe that key personal information about our customers, which have financial implications such as credit card numbers, credit card expiry dates, drivers license number, and social security number should be protected from unauthorized access. Therefore, we ensure that such information if only transferred between your Web browser and our Web server using the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) and is encrypted during all transfers.

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

You can send email to [Cellmania Support](mailto:support@cellmania.com).

## Cellmania Privacy Policy, including adherence to EU-US Safe Harbor Privacy Principles

**NOTICE:** Cellmania will inform individuals about the purposes for which it collects and uses information about them, the types of third parties to which it discloses the information, and individuals may restrict usage by contacting Cellmania. Individuals can contact Cellmania at 321 E Evelyn Ave, Mountain View, CA 94041, USA, or send email to [support@cellmania.com](mailto:support@cellmania.com) with any inquiries or complaints. Cellmania will not use information for purposes other that intended. 

**CHOICE:** Cellmania will not use information for purposes other that intended. If there does arise a situation where this is necessary,  Cellmania will offer individuals the opportunity to choose (opt out) whether their personal information is (a) to be disclosed to a third party(1) or (b) to be used for a purpose that is incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by the individual. Individuals will be provided with clear and conspicuous, readily available, and affordable mechanisms to exercise choice.

Cellmania has a policy of not collecting sensitive information. Should a need arise to collect sensitive information (i.e. personal information specifying medical or health conditions, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership or information specifying the sex life of the individual), individuals will be given affirmative or explicit (opt in) choice if the information is to be disclosed to a third party or used for a purpose other than those for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by the individual through the exercise of opt in choice. In any case, Cellmania will treat as sensitive any information received from a third party where the third party treats and identifies it as sensitive. 

**ONWARD TRANSFER:** To disclose information to a third party, Cellmania will apply the Notice and Choice Principles above. Where Cellmania wishes to transfer information to a third party that is acting as an agent, as described in the endnote, it may do so if it first either ascertains that the third party subscribes to the Principles or is subject to the Directive or another adequacy finding or enters into a written agreement with such third party requiring that the third party provide at least the same level of privacy protection as is required by the relevant Principles.If Cellmania complies with these requirements, it shall not be held responsible (unless Cellmania agrees otherwise) when a third party to which it transfers such information processes it in a way contrary to any restrictions or representations, unless Cellmania knew or should have known the third party would process it in such a contrary way and the Cellmania has not taken reasonable steps to prevent or stop such processing. 

**SECURITY:** When Cellmania creates, maintains, uses or disseminates personal information Cellmania will take reasonable precautions to protect it from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. 

**DATA INTEGRITY:** Consistent with the Principles, personal information must be relevant for the purposes for which it is to be used. Cellmania will not process personal information in a way that is incompatible with the purposes for which it has been collected or subsequently authorized by the individual. To the extent necessary for those purposes, Cellmania will take reasonable steps to ensure that data is reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete, and current. 

**ACCESS:** Individuals will have access to personal information about them that Cellmania holds and be able, by contacting Cellmania at [support@cellmania.com](mailto:support@cellmania.com) to correct, amend, or delete that information where it is inaccurate, except where the burden or expense of providing access would be disproportionate to the risks to the individual's privacy in the case in question, or where the rights of persons other than the individual would be violated. 

**ENFORCEMENT:** Cellmania has mechanisms for assuring compliance with the Principles, and recourse for individuals to whom the data relate affected by non-compliance with the Principles by contacting Cellmania. Cellmania will utilize the European Data Protection Authorities for dispute resolution for issues involving European Data Individual's complaints and disputes will be investigated and resolvedby reference to the Principles and damages awarded where the applicable law or private sector initiatives so provide; (b) Cellmania will institute relevant follow up procedures for verifying that the attestations and assertions businesses make about their privacy practices are true and that privacy practices have been implemented as presented.

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [Cellmania Support](mailto:support@cellmania.com)
